allthelyrics.com 2019-08-10

# Privacy Policy | All The Lyrics

Allthelyrics.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

## Use of Information

When you use allthelyrics.com, we may collect information about your use of the website in order to provide and improve our services. For example, we or our third party utility-tracking partners may collect your browser type and IP address through log files. This information is gathered for all allthelyrics.com visitors.

In order to register with our website, the visitor shall provide us with personal information which may include name, e-mail address, password, etc. We keep all such information strictly confidential and do not sell, share, transfer or distribute it to any third person.

## Third Party

We use Google AdSense, Google Analytics, Addthis, and other third-party companies to serve ads and services when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide services on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Also, they may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

## Links to Other Sites

This site contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our website and technologies easier by, among other things, saving your preferences for you. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. You may also opt-out from third party tracking via an industry-standard opt-out page such as the Network Advertising Initiative’s page accessible via its consumer website at www.networkadvertising.org.

## Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this website, you accept the policies and restrictions set forth in this online privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use website. 

We reserve the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time.
